<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<extension id="media_library" status="released" xmlns="http://getsymphony.com/schemas/extension/1.0">
	<name>Media Library</name>
	<description>Media management extension for Symphony CMS. Edit images and manage upload file.</description>
	<repo type="github">https://github.com/pixelninja/media_library</repo>
	<types>
		<type>Workflow</type>
	</types>
	<authors>
		<author>
			<name github="pixelninja" symphony="touchstone">Phillip Gray</name>
			<email>phill@thebold.nz</email>
			<website>https://thebold.nz</website>
		</author>
	</authors>
	<releases>
		<release version="2.1.0" date="2020-08-24" min="2.7.x">
			- Bug fix: prevent events being called multiple times
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.12" date="2020-08-24" min="2.7.x">
			- Consistent styling for fields within the Primary column
			- Add a landscape and portrait ratio with relevant validation
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.11" date="2020-08-03" min="2.7.x">
			- Remove icon from navigation
			- Add scripts/styles from local source instead of calling them from unpkg.com as it's often slow to load
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.10" date="2020-07-02" min="2.7.x">
			- Allow multiple files to be selected at once when field allows it
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.9" date="2020-06-23" min="2.7.x">
			- Add a check for animated GIFs into FilePond transform process, if it is then don't apply transform which converts it to a PNG.
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.8" date="2020-06-23" min="2.7.x">
			- Media Fields within Modal boxes weren't opening because of the `trigger` call on a non existant nav item. I have fixed this by wrapping the loading of the ML into a function and calling that on click instead.
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.7" date="2020-06-05" min="2.7.x">
			- Add ability to define a destinition folder for file selection
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.6" date="2020-05-11" min="2.7.x">
			- Create field specific validation for image ratio and file size
			- Bug fix: validation didn't loop through data array and only validated first item. It now validates all files attached.
			- Add better Doka crop ratios
			- Redo the read me
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.5" date="2020-05-06" min="2.7.x">
			- Bug fix: delete button event wasn't triggering on AJAX loaded content
			- Bug fix: rogue colon in delete file function causing an error
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.4" date="2020-05-06" min="2.7.x">
			- Better define jQuery
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.3" date="2020-05-06" min="2.7.x">
			- Add missing `Symphony::Configuration()->remove()` from Uninstall function
			- Add File Size validation
			- Add Image Size validation
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.2" date="2020-05-05" min="2.7.x">
			- Add a file_exists check for the Doka files to prevent unecessary requests which fail
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.1" date="2020-05-05" min="2.7.x">
			- Type fix where min image height was being applied to max image height
		</release>
		<release version="2.0.0" date="2020-05-05" min="2.7.x">
			- Replace upload method with FilePond
			- Include Doka integration, if user has a licence
			- Add preferences pane for image editing options
			- Some styling changes for better flow
			- Automatically refresh list of files on completion of upload
		</release>
		<release version="1.3.3" date="2020-04-15" min="2.7.x">
			- Sanitize the file name when uploading to prevent special characters causing display issues with images
		</release>
		<release version="1.3.2" date="2020-03-30" min="2.7.x">
			- Sanitize the file name to prevent errors in XML output, specifically the name attribute
		</release>
		<release version="1.3.1" date="2020-03-11" min="2.7.x">
			- Update how multiple items are displayed
			- Add drag/drop for reording multiple items
		</release>
		<release version="1.3" date="2020-03-10" min="2.7.x">
			- Add ability for multiple files to be attached
			- Add default preview so something is always displayed
		</release>
		<release version="1.2.2" date="2020-03-06" min="2.7.x">
			- Bug fix where ML wouldn't trigger within AJAX loaded content (e.g within Entry Relationship Field content)
		</release>
		<release version="1.2.1" date="2020-03-06" min="2.7.x">
			- Add validation to Media Library field
			- Add a remove link to unattach files
			- Show video and audio previews
			- Have bigger previews in the Primary column
		</release>
		<release version="1.2.0" date="2020-03-05" min="2.7.x">
			- Add a Media Library Field to the section editor
			- The new field triggers the ML which allows for uploading/selecting a file to attach to an entry
			- Show a preview of the file if it's an image
			- Output the field in a datasource with relevant meta data
		</release>
		<release version="1.1.3" date="2019-08-09" min="2.7.x">
			- Add a tag count to the Tags link, and add hover state showing tag content
			- Ignore changes to the json file
		</release>
		<release version="1.1.2" date="2019-08-07" min="2.7.x">
			- Tagging bug fixes
		</release>
		<release version="1.1.1" date="2019-08-07" min="2.7.x">
			- Tagging bug fixes
		</release>
		<release version="1.1" date="2019-08-06" min="2.7.x">
			- Added ability to tag images, which are searchable
		</release>
		<release version="1.0.1" date="2019-03-19" min="2.7.x">
			- Update so deleting works within lightbox
			- Bug fixes
		</release>
		<release version="1.0.0" date="2019-03-18" min="2.7.x">
			- Remove unused plugins and add clipboard into extension js file for fewer requests
			- Add AJAX call for page fetching
			- Combine this plugin with TinyMCE plugin to work within editors
		</release>
		<release version="0.4" date="2019-03-15" min="2.7.x">
			- Removed Featherlite, and open previews in a new tab instead
		</release>
		<release version="0.3" date="2019-03-15" min="2.7.x">
			- Order files by date instead of name
			- Hide directories by default. A button has been added for toggling their visibility
			- Added an input for filtering files based on a keyword match
		</release>
		<release version="0.2" date="2017-08-17" min="2.7.x">
			- Restructured the way files are displayed
			- Added loads of features
		</release>
		<release version="0.1" date="2017-07-22" min="2.7.x" />
	</releases>
</extension>
